(Leonard:)Where do I sign?
(Sheldon:)Right here. Use your finger.
- There. Done.
All right.
(Sheldon:)That's it. We are now
no longer companions, boon or otherwise.
(Sheldon:)We are now merely acquaintances.
(Sheldon:)To amend the words of Toy Story,
you have not got a friend in me.
- I'm gonna go home and take a nap.
- Yeah, well, tell it to someone who cares.
(Howard:)I got pretty exciting NASA news today.
(Howard:)Next week, I fly to Houston for orientation
and zero-gravity elimination drills.
- What does that mean?
- He's gonna learn to poop in space.
(Howard:)Open the pod bay doors, HAL.
(Raj:)Maybe your nickname
should be Brown Dynamite.
(Sheldon:)Hello, dear friends. And Dr. Hofstadter.
What's up?